app4free.ml 2018-02-18

# Privacy policy ~ Applications

**Personal Identification Information**

We may collect personal information for users across a variety of ways, including but not limited to when users visit the site, fill in forms, and also regarding the activities, services, features or resources available on the site. Users may be asked, - if necessary - the name and email address. However, users can visit our site anonymously. We collect personally identifiable information only from users who wish to do so. Users have the right to refuse to enter their personal data, but this may prevent them from participating and making use of some of the website services that require real data.

**Non-personal information**

We may save non-personal data to users when accessing the site. This may include the name of the browser, the type of computer, the technical information used to connect the user to the site, such as the operating system, Internet service providers, etc.

**Cookies for the browser**

The site may use the "cookies" system to improve the service for users. Browsers store cookies on a hard drive for record keeping and sometimes to track user information. The user may resort to adjusting browser settings to reject cookies or to alert when new cookies are sent, but this causes some important features to be disabled.

**How we use the information collected**

**[Applications](http://www.app4free.ml/)** collects personal data for users to use for the following purposes:

\- Customize user experience

We may use the data in aggregate to understand the nature of users' use of the services and resources provided on the Site.

\- Improved site performance

We always strive to improve site performance based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

\- Improving customer service

The information we receive helps us to respond more effectively to service requests and support needs.

**How we protect your data**

We adopt all means of data collection, security measures to protect against unauthorized access attempts, or attempts to destroy personal information such as user name, password as well as financial transactions and data stored on our site.

**Exchange your personal data**

We do not sell or trade personal data of our users to serve people or third parties. We only share public information that is not linked to any personal data related to visitors or members.

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to members through advertising partners who use cookies. These files allow the ad server to recognize your device every time ads are sent to you to collect your (non-personal) information. This information allows ad networks to deliver targeted ads that they think will be most useful to you.

**Google Adsense**

Some ads are served by Google. Google displays its ads based on user visits to our site or other sites. No personal data such as name, e-mail, actual address, etc. is used.

**Compliance with the Children's Privacy Protection Act**

Protecting the privacy of young people is very important, which is why we do not collect or retain any data about those we know are under 13, nor do we seek to attract users under 13!

**Change Privacy Policy**

We have the right to change the privacy policy at any time, and we will place the update date at the bottom of the page every time we make changes. Please check this page regularly to stay informed on how to provide support and persistent site attempts to protect member data.

**Approval of these Terms**

If you use the site, you will of course have agreed to this policy. If you do not agree with any of the above, please do not use the site!
